cpainstruments.com 2015-02-04

# CPA Instruments: Website Terms

We believe it is important that you know how we treat information about you which we receive via the Internet. Our commitment to personal privacy is paramount.

We use the information we collect about you to process your bonus and subscription requests and to provide a more personalized experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**What Information Do We Collect? How Do We Use It?**

You may voluntarily sign up to be informed about certain offers. For this service we need only an e-mail address and a name, which we use to send the information you requested. We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important changes to the Web site.

You can generally visit our Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, in certain sections of this Site, to use certain services, we may require you to register for an account, or we may invite you to submit questions or comments or request information, participate in surveys, questionnaires or contests, subscribe to newsletters or participate in community forums. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may ask that you complete and submit an online form with personally identifiable information such as your name, username, email address, contact information and credit card information. 

**Will Company Disclose the Information it Collects to Outside Parties?**

Our company does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by CPAInstruments.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**In Summary**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site so that the promised bonuses/information/products reach you safely and to enhance your overall experience. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others.

CPAInstruments.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time by providing notice of such modification on this site.  
Copyright © 2012 All Rights Reserved. MarkAce Marketing Pvt. Ltd.
